

# Mark Salvaña DEVELOPER, CONSULTANT & MENTOR



**Age:** 32

Mobile: +639198602609 (PH) Email: email@marksalvana.com Addess: Mandaluyong, Metro Manila

Philippines, 1550

**Website:** https://marksalvana.com

twitter.com/lBigByte

linkedin.com/in/marksalvana/

github.com/marksalvana

# **Education**

Mapua Institute of Technology 2012-2017

**Philippines Science High School** 2004-2008

#### Stacks

#### Languages

PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS3, MySQL, Svelte, MongoDB, Typescript

### **Frameworks**

Laravel, React, SvelteKit Express, Node, Tailwind

#### **Platforms**

Wordpress, OctoberCMS, Drupal

## **About**

Experienced and passionate web developer with more than 10 years experience. While it may feel a bit self-serving to talk about my accomplishments, I genuinely strive to make a positive impact through my work. I am dedicated to refining my skills, embracing challenges, and making a difference in the ever-evolving landscape of software development

# Skills/Expertise

🚣 Full-Stack Web Development

Skilled in Frontend and Backend Development using Laravel, Sveltekit, Wordpress, October, Shopify

Al Automation & Development

Knowledge response, Chatbot development & Model tuning using LangChain and GPT-3 | GPT 4

API Development

Build scalable APIs for your PWA or mobile aps using PHP, NodeJS, Eloquent, MongoDB and MySQL

Mentorship & Consultancy Solutions Consultancy in Business Process Automation, Software development & Digital Marketing

# **Experience**

Please check marksalvana.com for the projects I was involved in during my stay on the companies mentioned below.

#### **GlobalWebforce**

Senior Web Developer 2020-2023

As a senior web developer at GlobalWebForce Australia, I lead in solution design, infrastructure development, and task delegation, ensuring efficient project execution and delivering high-quality web solutions

## Tech&Design

Proprietor 2018-2020 Following my tenure at EAA, I took the entrepreneurial path and founded Tech&Design, a web development and design business. Collaborating with a team of like-minded

# **Entrepreneurs Accounting Academy**

Operations Manager 2016-2018

**IT Supervisor** 2015-2016

Senior Web Developer 2012-2015

**Graphic Artist** 2010-2012

At EAA, I successfully held multiple roles from Operations Manager to Sales & Marketing Supervisor, Web Designer, and Graphic Artist. My adaptability, coupled with a passion for continuous learning, allows me to thrive in dynamic environments and contribute effectively to thecompany specially in the fields of Marketing, Web Development, and IT.